

INFO



Adress

Austin, Texas, United States



E - Mail

haha.dreamy@gmail.com

Top Skills

Web Services Java Xml

Language

English: Native or Bilingual

Levi Sanderson

Rust, Golang, Blockchain, Solana

Summary:

With 10+ years in software technologies, including web, mobile, and 8 years in blockchain. I've worked at two startups: a software service firm and a blockchain company. Formerly a chief scientist at a crypto exchange, my career began as a developer at Yahoo and PayPal. As CTO I have developed a layer one blockchain using rust. Currently implementing Atomic DEX for Solana.

Experience:

OneNet Inc.

Rust Golang & Blockchain developer July 2019 - Present

Developing Atomic DEX for Solana.

https://github.com/r2st/etomic-swap-solana

Developed PoS Layer one blockchain using rust.

Developed XRPL bridge for Root network

Developed blockchain based mobile data marketplace for GIANT protocol

Worked for composable finance.

Worked on distributed Oracle - ORML integration Implemented curve stable swap for parallel finance Developed a blockchain application for NXM Labs Developed Awesome, an Artificial Intelligent Messenger to

connect with existing & new people.

(Tensorflow, scikit learn, Opency)

Bytecode interpreter in Rust

https://github.com/sumaninster/bytecode-interpreter Bridge to transfer tokens

https://github.com/sumaninster/bridge

MLG Blockchain Consulting

Chief Technology Officer May 2018 - July 2019

Designed and developed Mailcoin for US Postal services Worked on a blockchain project for Anami Blockchain Helped companies to develop wallet applications

Unocoin

Chief Scientist September 2017 - May 2018

Excoflare

Chief Executive Officer & Founder June 2016 - August 2017

Performed research on Bitcoin and other Blockchain Technologies (Hyperledger, Ethereum, Ripple, etc.).

CSC

Software Developer @ Paypal August 2015 - May 2016 (10 months) Worked on Paypal Merchant Features (C++/Linux)

Aztecsoft

Software Developer @ Yahoo June 2014 - May 2015 (1 year)

Worked @ Yahoo (Perl)
Worked on Pervasive Database Engine (C++/Windows)

Education:

Assam Engineering Institute

DOEACC A' Level, Computer Science · (2013 - 2014)

Biswanath College

Bachelor of Science - BS, Physics, Chemistry & Mathematics · (2010-2013)